Prudential Financial has lost I don't
know we're gonna say lost I think
they're happy too they lost its
so-called Sippy designation this just
crossing as a systemically important
financial institution that designation
had brought with it a lot of extra
supervision and regulation and
Prudential had maintained that it never
had met the standard for the city label
as you recall many financial firms did
not want to be labeled as asipi they are
saying now though that the this decision
for no longer to be asipi is a quote
appropriate one so that should actually
it hasn't moved the stock just yet but
potentially it will no more annual
stress tests there's also a couple other
things that they don't have
you